Who else wants one of my special homemade brownies?
還有誰想要我特製的自製布朗尼蛋糕嗎？
I will have one.
我會擁有一個。
Ah!
啊!
Yeah, I'm not going to have one.
是的，我不會擁有一個。
No, no, it's just my tooth.
不，不，這只是我的牙齒。
All right, I'll have one.
好吧，我也來一份。
So, what's the matter?
那麼，到底是怎麼一回事呢？
You need a dentist?
你需要看牙醫嗎？
I've got a good one.
我有一個很好的。
Oh, thanks.
哦，謝謝。
I have a good one, too.
我也有一個不錯的
I just, I...
我只是，我...
I can't see him.
我看不見他。
See, that is the problem with invisible dentists.
看，這就是隱形牙醫的問題。
You know, it's very unsettling to see all those metal tools just, you
你知道，看到所有這些金屬工具，你會感到非常不安
know, flying around.
知道，飛來飛去。
Why?
為什麼？
Why can't you go to him?
為什麼你不能去找他？
Because every time I go to the dentist, somebody dies.
因為每次去看牙醫，都會有人死。
That is so weird, because every time I go to the dentist, I
這太奇怪了 因為每次我去看牙醫
look down the hygienist's blouse.
看看衛生員的襯衫。
Phoebe, what, um...
菲比，什麼，嗯...
what?
什麼？
Yeah, yeah, first there was my Aunt Mary, and then there was, um,
是的，是的，首先是我的瑪麗阿姨，然後是，嗯，
John, my mailman, and then my, my cowboy friend, Albino Bob.
約翰，我的郵差，然後是我的牛仔朋友，白化病鮑伯。
And all of these people actually died?
而這些人竟然都死了？
Yes, while I was in the chair.
是的，當我坐在椅子上時。
That's why I take such good care of my teeth now, you know?
這就是為什麼我現在非常照顧我的牙齒，你知道嗎？
It's not about oral hygiene.
這與口腔衛生無關。
I floss to save lives.
我使用牙線來拯救生命。
Pheebs, come on, you didn't kill anybody.
菲比，得了吧，你沒有殺任何人。
These people just happened to die when you went to the dentist.
當你去看牙醫時，這些人就碰巧死了。
It's, it's just a coincidence.
這，這只是一個巧合。
Well, tell that to them.
好吧，告訴他們。
Oh, you can't, they're dead.
哦，你不能，他們已經死了。
I'll be there for you.
我會在那等你。
When the rain starts to pour.
當雨開始傾盆而下。
I'll be there for you.
我會在那等你。
Like I've never been there before.
就像我以前從未來過那裡一樣。
I'll be there for you.
我會在那等你。
Cause you're there for me, too.
因為你也在我身邊。
Thanks, Gunther.
謝謝，岡瑟。
Hi.
你好。
Hey.
嘿。
Um, can I get a napkin, too?
嗯，我也可以拿張餐巾紙嗎？
Oh, like you don't already have everything.
哦，就像你還沒有擁有一切一樣。
Ow!
噢！
Judy, you're in pain.
朱迪，你很痛苦。
Would you just go to the dentist?
你只是去看牙醫嗎？
Just go.
走吧。
All right, fine, fine.
好吧，好吧，好吧。
But if you're my next victim, don't come back as a poltergeist like
但如果你是我的下一個受害者，請不要以像這樣的惡作劇者的身份回來
sucks me into the TV set.
把我吸進電視機裡。
I promise.
我保證。
Although don't feel like you can't visit.
雖然不覺得不能參觀。
Hey, is Chandler here?
嘿，錢德勒在嗎？
No, no he's not.
不，不，他不是。
Guys, Joey just saw Janice kissing her ex-husband.
夥計們，喬伊剛剛看到珍妮絲親吻她的前夫。
What?
什麼？
Oh!
哦！
So what are you going to do?
那你要做什麼？
I mean, how are you going to tell Chandler?
我是說，你要怎麼告訴錢德勒？
I was thinking about that, and I think the best way would be
我正在考慮這個問題，我認為最好的方法是
to not.
不。
Joey, you can't keep this to yourself.
喬伊，你不能把這件事留給自己。
If you know about this, you have to tell him.
如果你知道這件事，就必須告訴他。
It'll kill him.
這會殺了他。
I mean, it'll just kill him.
我的意思是，這只會殺了他。
Well, you could wait till I go to the dentist.
好吧，你可以等我去看牙醫。
Maybe I'll kill him.
也許我會殺了他。
Oh!
哦！
Ugly naked guy's using his new hammock.
醜陋的裸體傢伙正在使用他的新吊床。
It's like a Play-Doh fat factory.
它就像培樂多脂肪工廠。
Well, I'm going to the dentist, so listen, okay?
好吧，我要去看牙醫，聽我說，好嗎？
Just be on the lookout for anything that you could fall into.
留意任何你可能陷入的事情。
Or that can fall on you.
或者這會落在你身上。
Or...
或者...
Just look out!
小心點！
And I also just want to...
而我也只是想...
I just want to tell you...
我只是想告訴你...
Tell you about that, um...
告訴你這個，嗯...
Okay, I have a problem.
好吧，我有一個問題。
I have to go into work for a few hours.
我必須去工作幾個小時。
Some kids messed up the Homo sapien display.
有些孩子弄亂了智人展示。
What did they do?
他們做了什麼？
Well, they painted over the word sapien for one thing.
好吧，他們把「智人」這個詞塗掉是為了一件事。
Then they...
然後他們...
Rearranged the figures.
重新排列了數字。
Let's just leave it at that.
我們就這樣吧。
So do you want me to watch Ben for you?
那你想讓我幫你照看本嗎？
Yes, that's what I was going to ask.
是的，這就是我要問的。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Whoa, wait, hello!
哇，等等，你好！
What about me?
關於我的什麼？
You.
你。
You want to watch Ben.
你想看本。
Yes, that'd be great.
是的，那就太好了。
You know, I just asked Monica because I know how empty her life
你知道，我只是問莫妮卡，因為我知道她的生活有多空虛
is.
是。
Hey, hey, Ross.
嘿，嘿，羅斯。
Yeah?
是的？
I got a science question.
我有一個科學問題。
If the Homo sapiens were, in fact, Homo sapiens...
如果智人其實就是智人…
Is that why they're extinct?
這就是它們滅絕的原因嗎？
Joey, Homo sapiens are people.
喬伊，智人也是人。
Hey, I'm not judging.
嘿，我不是評判。
Look, Benny, spoon.
看，本尼，湯匙。
Spoon.
湯匙。
Come on.
快點。
All right, you know what?
好吧，你知道嗎？
I think he's bored.
我覺得他很無聊。
Ben, you going to play the airplane game?
本，你要玩飛機遊戲嗎？
You want to show Rachel?
你想給瑞秋看嗎？
Come here.
過來吧。
You're going to do something fun.
你要做一些有趣的事。
Okay.
好的。
Wee-haw!
嗚嗚嗚！
Oh, so brave.
噢，真勇敢。
You're so brave.
你真勇敢。
Yes, you are.
是的，你是。
You're so brave.
你真勇敢。
Okay, okay.
好吧，好吧。
He's fine.
他很好。
Let's just put him down.
我們把他放下吧。
Come here, babe.
到這裡來，寶貝。
Yes, you're such a good boy.
是的，你真是個好孩子。
How could you do that to him?
你怎麼可以這樣對他？
Why is he stressing me?
他為什麼要給我壓力？
What is he going to say?
他要說什麼？
He's not going to say anything because we're not going to tell him.
他不會說什麼，因為我們不會告訴他。
We're not?
我們不是嗎？
No, we're not.
不，我們不是。
All right, I like that.
好吧，我喜歡這樣。
So we're okay.
所以我們沒事。
We're okay.
我們沒事。
We're okay, aren't we?
我們沒事，不是嗎？
No, we're not okay.
不，我們不好。
We're not okay.
我們不好。
There's a bump.
有一個腫塊。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Push it in!
推進去！
You cannot push it in!
你推不進去！
Okay.
好的。
We're going to need a distraction.
我們需要分散注意力。
Okay.
好的。
That's it.
就是這樣。
Okay.
好的。
I got it.
我得到了它。
Okay.
好的。
The second that Ross walks in that door, I want you to take
羅斯走進那扇門的那一刻，我希望你能接受
him back to your bedroom and you do whatever it is that you
他回到你的臥室，你就做你該做的事
do that makes him go, Reeee!
這樣做能讓他走，Reeee！
Or...
或者...
we could put a hat on his head.
我們可以把帽子戴在他頭上。
A hat.
一頂帽子。
Yes!
是的！
We need a hat.
我們需要一頂帽子。
Where are we going to find a tiny little hat?
我們要去哪裡去找一頂小帽子呢？
I'll get Rainy Day Bear.
我會得到雨天熊。
I guess he'll know what to do.
我想他會知道該怎麼做。
Oh, my God, you're a genius!
天哪，你真是個天才！
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
It's kind of sewn on, though.
不過，它有點像是縫上去的。
Give it.
給吧。
Okay.
好的。
Oh!
哦！
Oh, it's just like a bloodbath in here today.
哦，今天這裡就像一場大屠殺。
Hey, hold on a second.
嘿，等一下。
Hold on a second.
等一下。
Do you think these pearls are nice?
你覺得這些珍珠好看嗎？
I'd really prefer a mountain bike.
我真的比較喜歡登山車。
Janice's birthday is coming up.
珍妮絲的生日快到了。
I want to get her something special.
我想送她一些特別的東西。
Come in here with me.
跟我一起到這裡來吧。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
哇哇哇，等等。
Whoa.
哇哦。
What?
什麼？
You want to get her something special.
你想送她一些特別的東西。
Get her flowers.
給她送花。
Get her candy.
給她拿糖果。
Get her gum.
給她拿口香糖。
Girls love gum.
女孩子都喜歡口香糖。
That's a good idea.
這是個好主意。
Dear Janice, have a hubba-bubba birthday.
親愛的珍妮絲，祝你生日快樂。
I would like to get her something serious.
我想給她一些嚴肅的事情。
Oh, you want something serious.
哦，你想要一些嚴肅的事情。
You know what you should do?
你知道你該做什麼嗎？
You should get her one of those, um...
你應該買一件，嗯...
barium enemas.
鋇劑灌腸。
Those are dead serious.
這些都是非常嚴重的。
And you know she'll never get one for herself.
你知道她永遠不會為自己得到一個。
Look, I'm going to go in here and you don't buy me anything
聽著，我要進去，你不給我買任何東西
ever.
曾經。
No, no, you can't.
不，不，你不能。
You can't.
你不能。
You can't buy her pearls.
你買不到她的珍珠。
You just can't.
你就是不能。
You can't.
你不能。
Why not?
為什麼不呢？
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
Uh, okay.
呃，好吧。
Here's the thing.
事情是這樣的。
This is the thing.
就是這樣。
Okay, the thing is...
好吧，事情是…
What is the thing?
到底是怎麼回事？
Okay.
好的。
I went down to the Mattress King showroom and...
我去了床墊王陳列室，然後…
and I saw Janice kissing her ex-husband.
我看到珍妮絲正在親吻她的前夫。
What?
什麼？
They were in his office.
他們在他的辦公室。
Well, she...
嗯，她...
she wouldn't do that.
她不會那樣做。
She's...
她是...
she's with me.
她和我在一起。
I'm telling you, man.
我告訴你，夥計。
I saw it.
我看到了。
Yeah, well, you're wrong.
是的，好吧，你錯了。
Okay?
好的？
You're wrong.
你錯了。
I'm not wrong.
我沒有錯。
I wish I was.
我希望我是。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
Bet that barium enema doesn't sound so bad now, huh?
我敢打賭，鋇灌腸現在聽起來沒那麼糟了，對吧？
It just makes more sense as an ensemble.
作為一個整體，它才更有意義。
Besides, it takes the focus off the hat.
此外，它還分散了人們對帽子的注意力。
No.
不。
Oh!
哦！
You're alive!
你還活著！
See, babes?
看到了嗎，寶貝們？
I promised you no one would die, didn't I?
我答應過你沒有人會死，不是嗎？
Yeah, well, we'll see about that.
是的，好吧，我們會看看的。
Can I use your phone?
我可以使用你的電話嗎？
Just want to call everyone I know.
只是想打電話給我認識的每個人。
Sure.
當然。
We have no money.
我們沒有錢。
Go ahead.
前進。
Hey, you're not dead.
嘿，你還沒死。
Okay, see ya.
好的，再見。
Monica.
莫妮卡。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
He just said my name.
他只說了我的名字。
Did you hear that?
你聽到了嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Monica Bang.
莫妮卡·邦。
Okay, I heard that.
好吧，我聽到了。
Did he just say Monica Bang?
他剛才是說莫妮卡·邦嗎？
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
Oh, my God, he's gonna rat me out.
哦，天哪，他會出賣我的。
Monica Bang.
莫妮卡·邦。
Oh.
哦。
Sweetie.
親愛的。
Sweetie, you need to stop saying that now.
親愛的，你現在不能再這麼說了。
That's no big deal.
這沒什麼大不了的。
It's not even worth mentioning.
這甚至不值得一提。
You see, we all do it all the time.
你看，我們一直都這樣做。
See?
看？
Watch this.
注意這個。
Watch, watch, watch.
看，看，看。
Pin!
別針！
Ow!
噢！
Monica Bang!
莫妮卡邦！
Everybody Bang!
大家邦！
Bin Bang!
賓邦！
Rachel Bang!
雷切爾邦！
Bang, Rachel Bang!
砰，雷切爾砰！
Oh, isn't it fun?
哦，不是很有趣嗎？
Look at that!
看看那個！
We all do it.
我們都這麼做。
Okay, I'm stopping now.
好吧，我現在停下來。
You okay?
你還好嗎？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
You know, if it's not a headboard, it's just not worth it.
你知道，如果不是床頭板，那就不值得。
How's my ding-a-ling?
我的叮叮鈴怎麼樣？
Uh...
呃...
I don't know.
我不知道。
You tell me.
你告訴我。
Anything you, uh, want to tell me?
有什麼想告訴我的嗎？
Because if you, uh, you should...
因為如果你，呃，你應該...
If you...
如果你...
You tell me.
你告訴我。
Why are your eyes so wide?
你的眼睛怎麼這麼大？
You tell me.
你告訴我。
Maybe it's because I was just fooling around with my ex.
也許是因為我只是跟我的前任鬼混。
Oh, no, no, no!
哦，不，不，不！
No, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不！
That was you!
那是你！
All right.
好的。
How did you know?
你怎麼知道的？
Joey told me.
喬伊告訴我的。
He saw you two kissing.
他看見你們兩個接吻了。
In the park?
在公園裡？
No, in his office.
不，在他的辦公室。
How many kisses were there?
有多少個吻？
Just those two.
就他們兩個。
Why?
為什麼？
Why was there kissing?
為什麼會有接吻？
There should be no kissing.
不應該有接吻。
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
哦，對不起，親愛的。
I'm so, so...
我是這樣，這樣…
Ah!
啊!
I'm so, so sorry.
我非常非常抱歉。
I just...
我只是...
Ah!
啊!
But I...
但我...
Oh, what happened was...
哦，發生了什麼事…
I can't...
我不能...
I can't breathe.
我無法呼吸。
Can you get me a bag or something?
你能給我一個包包什麼的嗎？
Here, here.
這裡，這裡。
Here.
這裡。
Let me see.
讓我看看。
I'll take it.
我要買它。
Look, I've got to know.
聽著，我必須知道。
Are you finished with me?
你跟我說完了嗎？
Are you finished with him?
你和他結束了嗎？
Do you still love him?
你還愛他嗎？
Do you still love me?
你還愛我嗎？
All right, look.
好吧，看吧。
I'm gonna need an actual answer here, okay?
我需要一個真正的答案，好嗎？
So, which is it?
那麼，是哪一個呢？
Him or me?
他還是我？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Okay.
好的。
If you're alive, you answer your phone!
如果你還活著，你就接聽電話！
Okay, Ben.
好吧，本。
I won't tell your daddy that you had ice cream before dinner if
我不會告訴你爸爸你晚餐前吃了冰淇淋，如果
you won't tell him about our little bonking incident.
你不會告訴他我們的小事。
Monica, number one, I don't think Ben understands the concept of bribery.
莫妮卡，第一，我認為本來不理解賄賂的概念。
And number two, I...
第二，我...
What?
什麼？
You said number two.
你說的是第二個。
I also said number one.
我也說第一名。
I know.
我知道。
Hey, everyone.
嘿，大家。
Hi!
你好！
How's my little boy?
我的小男孩怎麼樣了？
He's perfect.
他很完美。
Aren't you, Ben?
你不是嗎，本？
He's never been better.
他從來沒有這麼好過。
What'd you do, take him whaling?
你做了什麼，帶他去捕鯨？
Monica.
莫妮卡。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
He just said your name.
他只是說了你的名字。
That's great.
那太棒了。
Good job, Ben.
幹得好，本。
Monica Bay.
莫妮卡灣。
Oh, that's right.
哦，是這樣。
That's what I'd sound like if I exploded.
如果我爆炸的話，我聽起來就是這樣。
Woo-hoo!
嗚呼！
The curse is broken.
詛咒被打破了。
I called everybody I know, and everyone is alive.
我給我認識的每個人都打了電話，每個人都還活著。
Huh.
呵呵。
What?
什麼？
Ugly naked guy looks awfully familiar.
醜陋的裸體男人看起來非常熟悉。
He's still.
他還在。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I killed him.
我殺了他。
I killed another one.
我又殺了一個。
And this curse is getting stronger, too.
而這個詛咒也越來越強烈。
To bring down something that big?
要把這麼大的東西打倒嗎？
Maybe he's just taking a nap.
也許他只是在小睡。
I'm telling you, he hasn't moved since this morning.
我告訴你，他從今天早上起就沒有動過。
We should call somebody.
我們應該打電話給某人。
And tell them what?
並告訴他們什麼？
That the naked guy we stare at all the time isn't moving?
我們一直盯著的那個裸體男人一動也不動？
We've got to find out if he's alive.
我們必須找出他是否還活著
Yeah, but how are we going to do that?
是的，但是我們該怎麼做呢？
There's no way.
沒辦法啊
Well, there is one way.
嗯，有一種方法。
His window's open.
他的窗戶開著。
I say we poke him.
我說我們戳他。
Hey.
嘿。
You know how we save all those chopsticks for no reason when we
你知道當我們
get Chinese food?
吃中餐嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Well, now we got a reason.
好吧，現在我們有了理由。
What?
什麼？
Well, we're fashioning a very long poking device.
嗯，我們正在製作一個很長的戳戳裝置。
All right.
好的。
Hey, uh, what's the matter?
嘿，呃，怎麼了？
I talked to Janice.
我和珍妮絲談過。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Is she going back to him?
她要回到他身邊嗎？
She doesn't know.
她不知道。
Says she loves us both.
說她愛我們倆。
You know, I woke up this morning.
你知道嗎，我今天早上就醒了。
I was in love.
我戀愛了。
You know, I was happy.
你知道，我很高興。
You know, it serves me right for buying that 12-pack of condoms.
你知道，我買那個 12 片裝的保險套是對的。
And now I can't even return them because you choked on the receipt.
現在我甚至無法歸還它們，因為你被收據噎住了。
What are you, uh, what are you going to do?
你是什麼，呃，你要做什麼？
I don't know.
我不知道。
You know, what would you do?
你知道，你會做什麼？
It doesn't matter what I'd do.
我會做什麼並不重要。
Come on, come on, tell me.
來吧，來吧，告訴我。
All right, you're, uh, probably not going to want to hear this, but,
好吧，你，呃，可能不想聽這個，但是，
uh, if it was me, and this is just me, I would, uh,
呃，如果是我，這就是我，我會，呃，
I would bow out.
我會退出。
What?
什麼？
What are you, what are you talking about?
你是什麼，你在說什麼？
They have a kid together.
他們有一個孩子。
You know?
你知道？
They're like, they're like a family.
他們就像，他們就像一家人。
And if, I don't know, if there's a chance they can make that
我不知道他們是否有機會做到這一點
work, I know I wouldn't want to be the guy who stood in
工作，我知道我不想成為那個站出來的人
the way of that.
那樣的方式。
You okay?
你還好嗎？
You, uh, you want to come poke a nude guy?
你，呃，你想來戳一個裸體男人嗎？
Well, he's finally in sleep.
還好，他終於睡著了。
How about that, uh, bump on his head?
呃，他頭上的腫塊怎麼樣？
Are you, are you, are you sure it's a nude bump?
你，你，你確定這是裸體腫塊嗎？
I mean, no offense, but I've always thought of Ben as a fairly
我的意思是，無意冒犯，但我一直認為本是個相當不錯的人。
bumpy-headed child.
腦袋凹凸不平的孩子。
It's okay if he bumps his head.
如果他撞到頭也沒關係。
Kids bump their heads all the time, you know?
小孩子總是撞頭，你知道嗎？
It was your first time babysitting.
這是你第一次照顧孩子。
I'm sure you did the best you could.
我確信你已經盡力了。
I did.
我做到了。
I know.
我知道。
He's saying you have to watch them all the time.
他說你必須一直看著他們。
I did.
我做到了。
I watched.
我看了。
I watched, I watched Monica bang his head against that thing.
我看著，我看著莫妮卡用頭撞那個東西。
Monica did it?
莫妮卡幹的嗎？
Monica?
莫妮卡？
Yeah?
是的？
Um, did you notice anything weird about, about Ben today?
嗯，你今天有沒有註意到本有什麼奇怪的地方？
No, why?
不，為什麼？
Well, I was just playing with him, and, you know, we were doing
好吧，我只是和他一起玩，而且，你知道，我們正在做
the alphabet song, which he used to be really good at, but suddenly
字母歌，他以前很擅長，但突然
he's leaving out E and F.
他遺漏了E和F。
It's like they just, uh, I don't know, fell out of his head.
就好像它們只是，呃，我不知道，從他的腦子裡掉了下來。
Really?
真的嗎？
Oh, and also, he's, he's walking kind of funny.
哦，還有，他走路的樣子很有趣。
I mean, it's like his, his left leg is moving a lot faster
我的意思是，就像他的一樣，他的左腿移動得更快
than his right leg.
比他的右腿。
Yeah, he's in there, just sort of, you know.
是的，他就在那裡，你知道。
Oh, my God, I wrecked your baby!
天哪，我毀了你的孩子！
I hope it's still funny when you're in hell.
我希望當你身處地獄時它仍然很有趣。
You jerk.
你這個混蛋。
You know how much I love that kid, but it's a baby!
你知道我有多愛那個孩子，但那隻是個嬰兒！
No, Moncafe, Moncafe!
不，蒙卡夫，蒙卡夫！
Ow.
噢。
I'll get the hat.
我去拿帽子。
Janice, I have something I need to tell you, and I want you
珍妮絲，我有件事要告訴你，我想要你
to let me get through it, because it's, it's, it's not gonna be
讓我度過難關，因為它是，它是，它不會是
easy.
簡單的。
Okay.
好的。
I think you should go back with Gary.
我認為你應該和加里一起回去。
I don't want to be the guy that breaks up a family.
我不想成為拆散家庭的人。
You know, when my parents split up, it was because of that guy.
你知道，我父母分手的時候，就是因為那個人。
Whenever I would see him, I would always think, you know, you're the
每當我看到他時，我總是會想，你知道，你就是那個
reason.
原因。
You are why they're not together.
你就是他們不在一起的原因。
And I, I hated that guy.
而我，我討厭那個傢伙。
And it didn't matter how nice he was or, you know, how happy
他有多好，或者，你知道，有多快樂，並不重要
he made my dad.
他創造了我的父親。
Wow.
哇。
Yeah, wow.
是的，哇。
It's the right thing to do.
這是正確的做法。
Uh, you're right.
呃，你是對的。
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
But before I can say goodbye, there's something I really need you to
但在我說再見之前，我真的需要你做一件事
know, Chandler.
知道嗎，錢德勒。
The way I feel about you, it's like, I finally understand what Lionel
我對你的感覺就像是，我終於明白了萊昂內爾的意思
Richie's been singing about.
裡奇一直在唱歌。
You know, I mean, what we have, it's like movie love.
你知道，我的意思是，我們擁有的，就像電影裡的愛情。
You're my soulmate.
你是我的靈魂伴侶。
And I can't believe we're not gonna be spending the rest of our
我不敢相信我們不會花掉剩下的錢
lives together.
住在一起。
Then don't leave me.
那就別離開我。
What?
什麼？
Forget what I said.
忘記我說的話了。
I was babbling.
我胡言亂語。
Pick me.
選我吧
No, you were right.
不，你是對的。
You were right.
你是對的。
I mean, I gotta give my marriage another chance.
我的意思是，我得再給我的婚姻一次機會。
No, you don't.
不，你不知道。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
I say you have to give your divorce another chance.
我說你必須再給離婚一次機會。
You should not have to settle for just half my heart.
你不應該只滿足於我的一半心。
I'll settle for half your heart.
我會滿足你的一半心。
I'll settle for a quarter of your heart.
我就滿足於你的四分之一的心。
I'll settle for a little, a tiny, a ventricle.
我會滿足於一點點，一點點，一個心室。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Oh, don't go.
噢，別走。
I gotta go.
我得走了。
No.
不。
No, no.
不，不。
Honey, honey.
親愛的，親愛的。
People are looking.
人們正在尋找。
I don't care.
我不在乎。
I don't care!
我不在乎！
Yeah, um, okay.
是的，嗯，好吧。
I'm, I'm leaving.
我，我走了。
You can't leave!
你不能離開！
I have your shoe!
我有你的鞋子！
Goodbye, Chandler Bing.
再見，錢德勒·賓。
Rachel has those in Burgundy.
雷切爾在勃根地有那些。
All right, now remember.
好吧，現在記住了。
Something this big and long is gonna be very difficult to maneuver.
這麼大這麼長的東西，操縱起來會非常困難。
Fortunately, I have a lot of experience in that area.
幸運的是，我在這方面有很多經驗。
Are you 12 today?
今天你12歲了嗎？
Can we please focus here?
我們可以把注意力集中到這裡嗎？
A naked man's life hangs in the balance.
一個裸體男人的生命懸而未決。
I'm telling you, he's dead.
我告訴你，他死了。
What we're about to have here is a dead fat guy on a
我們即將看到的是一個死胖子騎在
stick.
戳。
All right, ladies and gentlemen, let's poke.
好吧，女士們先生們，讓我們戳一下吧。
Steady.
穩定的。
Okay, a little higher.
好吧，高一點。
Careful of the angle.
小心角度。
Okay, okay.
好吧，好吧。
We're approaching the window.
我們正在接近窗戶。
Thread the needle.
穿針。
He's alive!
他還活著！
And yet, we're still poking him.
然而，我們仍然在戳他。
Okay, retract the device.
好的，收回裝置。
Retract the device.
收回裝置。
He does not look happy.
他看起來並不高興。
Hey, hey!
嘿嘿！
Now he's showing us his poking device.
現在他正在向我們展示他的戳戳裝置。
Hey, that's never gonna make it all the way over here, buddy.
嘿，那是永遠不可能到達這裡的，夥計。
Hey!
嘿！
I'll hold you close in my arms I can't resist
我會把你緊緊抱在懷裡 我無法抗拒
your charm And love Love I'll be
你的魅力和愛愛我會的
a fool for you I'm sure You know I don't
我確信你對你來說是個傻瓜 你知道我不是
mind Oh, you know I don't mind Yes!
介意哦，你知道我不介意是的！
You mean the world to me Oh, I know I know I found
你對我來說意味著整個世界哦，我知道我知道我找到了
I found in you My endless love My
我在你身上找到了我無盡的愛
endless love Love Love Love Love
無盡的愛愛愛愛愛